Guide to the Foster Coffin papers, 1907-1961.
Coffin, Foster papers, 1907-1961.
Division of Rare and Manuscript Collections, Cornell University Library
Foster Coffin papers, 1907-1961.
41-2-1211
Foster, Coffin 1890-1979.
1 cubic ft.
Correspondence, financial records, a phonograph record, and a tape recording.
Division of Rare and Manuscript Collections, Cornell University Library
Correspondence with other members of the Cornell Class of 1912 concerning class activities, reunions, and the Donald C. Kerr Memorial Endowment; a small quantity of personal correspondence and financial records; and a phonograph record and tape recording of a portrait presentation ceremony.
BIOGRAPHICAL NOTE
Foster Coffin (class of 1912) was an Alumni Representative at Cornell University and was Director of Willard Straight Student Union, Cornell University.
COLLECTION DESCRIPTION
Correspondence with other members of the Cornell Class of 1912 concerning class activities, reunions, and the Donald C. Kerr Memorial Endowment; a small quantity of personal correspondence and financial records; and a phonograph record and tape recording of a portrait presentation ceremony.
SUBJECTS
Names:
Coffin, Foster, 1890-1979.; Cornell University--Alumni and alumnae.
INFORMATION FOR USERS
CONTAINER LIST
- Cornell 1912 Reunions, 1929 (Box 1, Folder 1)
- Cornell 1912 Reunions, 1930 (Box 1, Folder 2)
- Cornell 1912 Reunions, 1931 (Box 1, Folder 3)
- Cornell 1912 Reunions, 1931-1933 (Box 1, Folder 4)
- Cornell 1912 Reunions, 1934-1936 (Box 1, Folder 5)
- Cornell 1912 Reunions Miscellaneous, 1927-1931 (Box 1, Folder 6)
- Cornell 1912 Charles H. Blair for Alumni Trustee, 1934 (Box 1, Folder 7)
- Cornell 1912, Jan.-May 1937 (Box 1, Folder 8)
- Cornell 1912, June-Dec. 1937 (Box 1, Folder 9)
- Cornell 1912 Correspondence, 1938-1939 (Box 1, Folder 10)
- Cornell 1912 Miscellaneous, 1930-1937 (Box 1, Folder 11)
- Cornell 1912 Miscellaneous, 1934-1947 (Box 1, Folder 12)
- Cornell 1912, 1926 (Box 1, Folder 13)
- Cornell 1912, 1926-1927 (Box 1, Folder 14)
- Cornell 1912, Jan.-Mar. 1927 (Box 1, Folder 15)
- Cornell 1912, Apr.-June 1927 (Box 1, Folder 16)
- Cornell 1912 Tell Berna for Trustee, 1941 (Box 1, Folder 17)
- Cornell 1912 Miscellaneous, 1937-1951 (Box 1, Folder 18)
- Cornell 1912, 1939-1941 (Box 1, Folder 19)
- Cornell 1912, 1942-1946 (Box 1, Folder 20)
- Cornell 1912, Jan.-Mar. 1947 (Box 1, Folder 21)
- Cornell 1912, May-Dec. 1947 (Box 1, Folder 22)
- Cornell 1912, 1948-1949 (Box 1, Folder 23)
- Cornell 1912, 1950-1951 (Box 1, Folder 24)
- Cornell 1912, June-Dec. 1952 (Box 1, Folder 25)
- Cornell 1912, Jan.-May 1952 (Box 1, Folder 26)
- Cornell 1912 Miscellaneous, 1947 (Box 1, Folder 27)
- Donald C. Kerr Memorial Endowment, Foster M. Coffin, 1956 (Box 1, Folder 28)
- Donald C. Kerr Memorial Endowment, Foster M. Coffin, 1957 (Box 1, Folder 29)
- Donald C. Kerr Memorial Endowment Fund, 1958 (Box 1, Folder 30)
- Donald C. Kerr Memorial Endowment Fund, 1957 (Box 1, Folder 31)
- Donald C. Kerr Memorial Endowment Fund, 1957 (Box 1, Folder 32)
- Donald C. Kerr Memorial Endowment Fund - Active, 1958-1959 (Box 1, Folder 33)
- Donald C. Kerr Memorial Endowment Fund - Inactive, 1956-1957 (Box 1, Folder 34)
- Donald C. Kerr Memorial Endowment Fund - Inactive, 1958-1959 (Box 1, Folder 35)
- Bob Tschirky, 1961 (Box 1, Folder 36)
- Information re: bequests, 1935 (Box 1, Folder 37)
- Reunions, etc., 1935 (Box 1, Folder 38)
- Reunion Information - other schools (Box 1, Folder 39)
- Reunion Information - other schools (Box 1, Folder 40)
- Correspondence, 1927-1934 (Box 2, Folder 1)
- Correspondence, Mar. 1935 (Box 2, Folder 2)
- Correspondence, Apr.-May 1935 (Box 2, Folder 3)
- Correspondence, May 1935 (Box 2, Folder 4)
- Correspondence, June 1935 (Box 2, Folder 5)
- Correspondence, 1935 (Box 2, Folder 6)
- Correspondence, 1935 (Box 2, Folder 7)
- Miscellaneous Financial Records, 1927-1935 (Box 2, Folder 8)
- 1912 Class Photos, 1927-1957 (Box 2, Folder 9)
- 1912 Reunion Miscellaneous, 1926-1927 (Box 2, Folder 10)
- Miscellaneous, 1935 (Box 2, Folder 11)
- Personal Carver-Carruth Correspondence, 1907 (Box 2, Folder 12)
- World Wars Miscellaneous, 1918-1943 (Box 2, Folder 13)
- Personal Correspondence, 1934-1935 (Box 2, Folder 14)
- Personal - Insurance Policies, 1934-1935 (Box 2, Folder 15)
- Nantucket-Coffin Family Reunion, 1959 (Box 2, Folder 16)